{"cards":[{"mId":"674315ef-5507-435f-a9a5-e91662f84e8f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"hate","mBack":"Abhor"},{"mId":"248beee0-243f-48a7-8180-b922ec8c100f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"narrow-minded, prejudiced person","mBack":"Bigot"},{"mId":"746b9fde-aa76-4255-9cd2-e53f7991394f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"fake; false","mBack":"Counterfeit"},{"mId":"6c6fcf51-ed44-48bd-abe8-c99fcf18f714","mCardType":"text","mFront":"give voting rights","mBack":"Enfranchise"},{"mId":"598eec29-4bc3-4c7f-939f-a1d39c93dca1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"hinder; obstruct","mBack":"Hamper"},{"mId":"64b8d13d-80f2-49f5-a7c3-f24f58e3956c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to start a fire","mBack":"Kindle"},{"mId":"702b1bcb-8a29-474a-9ca8-6bbfbdebb3b0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"harmful; poisonous; lethal","mBack":"Noxious"},{"mId":"93505c47-c0e4-487d-861d-e80f4003baf0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"calm; peaceful","mBack":"Placid"},{"mId":"cc722d8a-e330-421d-bfad-c6230444e9ff","mCardType":"text","mFront":"payment for work done","mBack":"Remuneration"},{"mId":"621bd580-7f85-48ff-9237-3beaa9ca9160","mCardType":"text","mFront":"lucky charm","mBack":"Talisman"},{"mId":"2f09a953-7adb-429b-9ded-d8d9f92cd9cc","mCardType":"text","mFront":"rough; coarse; harsh","mBack":"Abrasive"},{"mId":"95a5bed9-59c8-4e93-a02e-292b943a3a84","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cheat; defraud","mBack":"Bilk"},{"mId":"be33d77f-0e4e-49f3-9ae2-087a12776967","mCardType":"text","mFront":"hidden; undercover","mBack":"Covert"},{"mId":"8e183d2f-543c-4d71-be72-db98c52a4548","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cause","mBack":"Engender"},{"mId":"ed937535-947a-49f7-b236-6bca01edc927","mCardType":"text","mFront":"storage area (like garage) for a plane","mBack":"Hangar"},{"mId":"48bd7ca2-30b5-43ec-8ed1-7bd1481d0e21","mCardType":"text","mFront":"complex; difficult to solve","mBack":"Knotty"},{"mId":"1b8a60a0-6cb2-4de4-afa3-c9803bf3b21b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"something subtle; a fine shade of meaning","mBack":"Nuance"},{"mId":"2930cba3-b8a3-4a29-83fd-bcd34c753745","mCardType":"text","mFront":"taking credit for someone else\u0027s writing or ideas","mBack":"Plagiarism"},{"mId":"34e5f29d-7f53-406d-8848-7a1343cb68e5","mCardType":"text","mFront":"fame","mBack":"Renown"},{"mId":"5f55c8c2-a6b0-44e8-9110-ec3772359d06","mCardType":"text","mFront":"going off the main subject","mBack":"Tangent"},{"mId":"b3d6e732-9234-425c-b8f1-a8523f9061f0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"humiliation; degradation","mBack":"Abasement"},{"mId":"facc29e0-e381-4a56-ba77-d2de26ec44a6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"swelling; fluttering; waving","mBack":"Billowing"},{"mId":"a48bc66b-5944-41d4-a326-a10cd9998eb1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"recoil in fear or servility; shrink away from","mBack":"Cower"},{"mId":"40d9e193-2135-466a-b48a-07d2f50ce361","mCardType":"text","mFront":"improve; make better or clearer","mBack":"Enhance"},{"mId":"4c130aaf-7a67-4646-a040-b546e5edc007","mCardType":"text","mFront":"noisy, attacking speech","mBack":"Harangue"},{"mId":"ece1b28f-d227-4d57-af00-779b15c6a58c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a maze","mBack":"Labyrinth"},{"mId":"7e1865c9-b585-4739-9a6e-b1dbfe214f71","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to counter; make unimportant","mBack":"Nullify"},{"mId":"45a56b8e-61b0-4f7d-b1a3-bce34ff130d1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"petitioner (in court of law)","mBack":"Plaintiff"},{"mId":"3d3cf1c1-a642-4ee5-9a5a-c422671cacf8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"full","mBack":"Replete"},{"mId":"0b5e7cc0-c5da-4cf9-9b52-7c1713316ef3","mCardType":"text","mFront":"can be touched","mBack":"Tangible"},{"mId":"ab512f40-de0b-43c5-bcaa-3a67f35f9f6e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cancel; deny; repeal","mBack":"Abrogate"},{"mId":"029ec46a-74a5-4572-be49-fdb35d684d78","mCardType":"text","mFront":"speech which offends religious sentiments","mBack":"Blasphemy"},{"mId":"f897da94-3bf9-4e8c-aa24-3e61f7fab8a9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"believable","mBack":"Credible"},{"mId":"e3edf39f-c3bf-44b2-9308-d8a57f43596e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"puzzle; mystery","mBack":"Enigma"},{"mId":"b100ed11-7330-44a9-a175-00f1faf39868","mCardType":"text","mFront":"indicators; bringers of warnings","mBack":"Harbingers"},{"mId":"662755da-df31-487a-9d67-d1cea61fe9b8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"complicated; highly convoluted","mBack":"Labyrinthine"},{"mId":"06270955-1b8f-49c7-9b14-8e93552c85d9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cuddle; snuggle","mBack":"Nuzzle"},{"mId":"db5166e5-9ea9-48ff-a892-f2d0401d3c66","mCardType":"text","mFront":"statement giving strong praise","mBack":"Plaudit"},{"mId":"c1d747e5-69f1-40fa-bcd1-8cb225492534","mCardType":"text","mFront":"shameful; very bad","mBack":"Reprehensible"},{"mId":"42e3edfc-885d-4aad-891a-08131e85e34a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"slow; late; overdue; delayed","mBack":"Tardy"},{"mId":"8602bab1-af36-45dc-9e6c-77b9c9272837","mCardType":"text","mFront":"desist; go without; withdraw","mBack":"Abstain"},{"mId":"3965cfe0-0a30-4862-b658-f367ba3aedbb","mCardType":"text","mFront":"damaged; destroyed; ruined","mBack":"Blighted"},{"mId":"61272ff2-3d52-47a7-bd57-59d743359ebf","mCardType":"text","mFront":"gullible; ready to believe anything","mBack":"Credulous"},{"mId":"c904942e-5ee6-4c1c-9ad6-62922572c704","mCardType":"text","mFront":"cover","mBack":"Enshroud"},{"mId":"ebf75b63-7829-415a-ae9d-93d757ea09ed","mCardType":"text","mFront":"arrogance; pride","mBack":"Haughtiness"},{"mId":"d275ecfc-734e-4d4b-97de-3196220c9e18","mCardType":"text","mFront":"tearful; sad","mBack":"Lachrymose"},{"mId":"59ea4cce-41de-4923-839c-7947b491fb51","mCardType":"text","mFront":"deliberately make something difficult to understand","mBack":"Obfuscate"},{"mId":"274e0aed-77d1-4609-971e-4f0f4206f727","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an excess","mBack":"Plethora"},{"mId":"a7419dfe-95bc-4696-8741-a58a9841d177","mCardType":"text","mFront":"shun; eschew","mBack":"Repudiate"},{"mId":"47d2bdae-e385-4df0-b2a0-24073cab9870","mCardType":"text","mFront":"boredom","mBack":"Tedium"}]}